agamimedia.com 2008-12-17

# Agami Media affiliate network - Privacy Policy

Last updated: **December 2008**

Agami Media strongly believes in every person's right to privacy. Within this Privacy Policy we explain our information collection technology and practices � the type of information that we collect, the way we store and use this information. We realize that the privacy of your personal information is very important and we will not treat this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Information We Collect**

The information collected on AgamiMedia.com is Publisher related personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Agami Media is the sole owner of all the data collected on this site.

Publishers wishing to join the Agami Media Publisher Network are required to provide personally identifiable information including name, address, phone number, e-mail address, tax ID number. 

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information. This information is anonymous; it is not connected with your personal information. Types of non-personally identifiable information we may collect, not exhaustive: 

  * The URL that you came to our site from.
  * Your IP address at the time you visited our site.
  * Pages from our site you visited and time you spent at each page.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small data files that a web site server stores on a computer. They contain information about activities performed by a user of the computer on the specific web site and characteristics of the computer at the time the user navigates the site. Examples: the IP address of the computer at the time the user navigates the site; the password the user has set for the site, so that the user doesn't have to type it each time he/she tries to log in at the site, etc. As cookies are data files, not code, they cannot erase or read information from a computer's hard drive or from other sites the computer user visits. Cookies can only be read by the server of the site that set them, so that information about activities on one site can't be transferred through a cookie to another site.

We may store two types of cookies on your computer: 

  * Session Cookies: These cookies are stored in the Internet browser and are deleted each time the browser is closed. We use session cookies mainly to facilitate site navigation: for example, once you log in to the site, you don't have to log in again during the same session; and to personalize site experience.
  * Permanent Cookies: These cookies are stored on the hard drive of your computer. They are not exactly "permanent". Each cookie has different "life span" determined by the web site that sets the cookie. We may use permanent cookies to store your username and password (encrypted) on your computer if you opt to have it saved.

We may use both types of cookies for aggregate audience analysis: where our visitors and Publishers come from, which pages they visit, how much time they spend on the site, etc. No personal information is stored in the cookies.

We may also use other technology (such as web beacons and tracker GIFs) to enhance the functionality of our site and to make Publisher activities on the site more convenient and efficient. 

**Use of the Information**

The Publisher personally identifiable information is used for business correspondence and for making payments to Publishers; it aids us to serve our Publishers in the most efficient and convenient way.

We use the non-personally identifiable information to enhance the functionality and usability of our site and to diagnose and prevent technical problems.

**Disclosure**

Agami Media will not share Publishers' personally identifiable information with any third parties except when required by law or as necessary to conduct business: to assist in normal and customary operational and statistical matters, or to provide administrative services such as billing and payments. Any third-party receiving such information will be required to treat it in a confidential and safeguarded manner, in accordance with industry standards and with the policies stated herein. If Agami Media or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity, Publisher information will be one of the transferred assets.

**Personal Information Updates**

You can modify or update your Personal Information after logging in to your Publisher account and going to  
Account Info > Edit Account.

**Personal Information Security**

Agami Media uses both proprietary technology and methods and Direct Track technology provided by Direct Response Technologies Inc. in order to collect and store information. Both Agami Media and Direct Response Technologies Inc. have implemented technical and managerial procedures in order to protect Publishers' personal information from unauthorized access and against loss, misuse or alteration. You can check out Direct Response Technologies Inc.'s Privacy Policy here: <http://www.directtrack.com/privacy.html>.

However, due to the open nature of the Internet, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, Agami Media cannot warrant that the information stored on our servers or transmitted to or from a user will be absolutely safe and both Agami Media and Direct Response Technologies Inc. disclaim any liability for any theft or loss, unauthorized access or damage, or interception of any data or communications. 

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Agami Media or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the AgamiMedia.com site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

**No Information Collected from Children**

In compliance with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)](http://www.coppa.org/coppa.htm) we will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain indication that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

By using the site you acknowledge your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. Agami Media reserves the right, at our only discretion to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at  
_[privacy@agamimedia.com](mailto:privacy@agamimedia.com)_.
